Finding Aid for the Sterling Silliphant Papers, 1957-1985
UCLA Library, Department of Special Collections
- Teleplays.
  - New Centurions
    - New Centurions - television. (Box 39)
  - Pearl, Addition, 11/82.
    - Episode I. n.p., undated; 117 pages. Typescript. (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Episode I. n.p., undated; 116 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Episode I. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 116 pages. Typescript (multilith) with typescript title page. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Episode I. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 123 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Episode I. n.p., 1978 April.; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 117 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith). (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - With revisions., May 1978. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Episode I. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 117 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith). (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - With revisions., 1978 May (Box 98, Folder 1)
        Nona Joy's copy.
    - Episode I. n.p., 1978 May 3; 116 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 113 pages. Typescript (photocopy). With white cover. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 115 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - With revisions., 1978 May (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 113 pages. Typescript. (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Revisions., 1978 May (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 113 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith), typescript (carbon). (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - With revisions., 1978 May (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 110 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 104 pages. Typescript. (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - With revisions., 1978 May (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 104 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 104 pages. Typescript (multilith). Wiht blue cover. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Episodes I, II, III. n.p., 1978 May 15; ca. 350 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Thursday. n.p., undated.; pages 88-157. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Thursday. n.p., undated.; pages 88-166. Typescript. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Thursday. n.p., undated.; pages 88-140. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Friday. n.p., undated.; pages 167-180. Typescript. (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Saturday. n.p., undated.; pages 224-321. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Saturday. n.p., undated.; pages 224-319. Typescript. (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Sunday. n.p., undated.; pages 320-489. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Sunday. n.p., undated.; pages 320-493. Typescript. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Sunday. n.p., undated.; pages 321-417. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Revised pages. n.p., ca. 1978 May; ca. 50 pages. Typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Revised pages. n.p., ca. 1978 May-June; ca. 75 pages. Typescript, typescript (carbon), (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Revised pages. n.p., ca. 1978 May-June; ca. 100 pages. Typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Revised pages. n.p., ca. 1978 May-June; ca. 100 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Episode I. n.p., ca. 1978; 116 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 101, Folder 7)
      "Rev. pgs. (old). See new yellows."
    - Episode II. n.p., ca. 1978; pages 3-110. Typescript (multilith). (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 May 1; pages 3-108. Typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 101, Folder 9)
      "Yellows-1st rev."
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 May 2; pages 3-104. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Episode III. n.p., undated; pages 3-104. Typescript (multilith). (Box 101, Folder 11)
      "Rev. pgs (old). See new yellows."
    - [Wednesday/Thursday] n.p., ca. 1978; pages 5-78. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Partial screenplay., ca. 1978; pages 2-104. Typescript. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Partial screenplay., ca. 1978; pages 2-112. Typescript. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Partial screenplay., ca. 1978; pages 3-104A. Typescript (carbon). (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Partial screenplay., ca. 1978; pages 3-110. Typescript (carbon). (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous pages of teleplay. n.p., undated.; pages 302-493. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous pages of teleplay. n.p., undated.; ca. 200 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous pages of teleplay. n.p., undated.; ca. 175 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous pages of teleplay. n.p., undated.; ca. 200 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Shooting schedule. Revised parts I, II, III. n.p., 1978 May-June; 77 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Production file. v.p., 1978; ca. 30 items. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 103, Folder 2)
      Includes second revised day-out-of-days schedule, location information sheet, research re name changes, artists deals memos.
  - Pearl Harbor, Addition, 11/82.
    - Pearl Harbor. n.p., 1977 November 14; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 124 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Pearl Harbor. n.p., 1977 November 15; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 118 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Pearl Harbor. n.p., 1977 November 15; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 124 pages. Typescript. (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Pearl Harbor. n.p., 1977 November 15; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 124 pages. Typescript (multilith). With white cover. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Pearl Harbor. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 126 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Pearl Harbor. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 123 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Episode I. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 123 pages. Typescript. (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Another copy., Typescript (multilith). With red cover. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Episode #2. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 113 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 115 pages. Typescript. (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 115 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Episode II. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 115 pages. Typescript (photocopy). With red cover. (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 124 pages. Typescript. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Episode Three. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 115 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 124 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Episode III. n.p., 1978 March; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 124 pages. Typescript (multilith). With red cover. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Pearl II, Addition, 11/82.
    - In time of war. n.p., 1979 January 16; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 54 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 103, Folder 3)
      Presentation of a novel for television.
    - In time of war. n.p., 1979 January 16; Written by Stirling Silliphant.; 57 pages. Typescript (photocopy). [2 copies.] (Box 103, Folder 4-5)
    - Partial outline of characters and action. n.p., undated; pages 17-[36]. Typescript, holograph. (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Pedigree Sheet
    - 1960 June 24., Typescript [teleplay] (Box 42)
  - Perry Mason Series, CBS-TV
    - 1957 March 1, 1 teleplay. (Box 1)
  - Rawhide, n.p.
    - 1964 April 26, 1 story outline with holograph corrections. (Box 16)
    - 1964 May 18, 1 teleplay with holograph corrections. (Box 16)
    - 1964 May 18, 1 teleplay. (Box 16)
    - 1964 April 26, 1 story outline (carbon). (Box 16)
    - 1964 September 14, 1 teleplay. (Box 16)
  - Route 66, Lancer Productions, Inc.
    - 1959 October 27 - 1963 September 23, 123 teleplays. (Box 6-15)
      Includes pilot for series.
      - The Searchers, 1959 October 27; (pilot script) (Box 6)
      - Black November, 1960 October 7; 4809 (Box 6)
      - A Lance of Straw, 1960 October 14; 4908 (Box 6)
      - The Swan Bed, 1960 October 21; 4935; (2 copies - one with corrections and insertions.) (Box 6)
      - The Man on the Monkey Board, 1960 October 28; 4933 (Box 6)
      - The Strengthening Angels, 1960 November 4; 4959 (Box 6)
      - The Drops of Water, 1960 November 11; 4932 (Box 6)
      - Three Sides, 1960 November 18; 4955 (Box 6)
      - Legacy for Lucia, 1960 November 25; 4907 (Box 6)
      - Layout at Glen Canyon, 1960 December 2; 4991; (2 copies) (Box 6)
      - The Beryllium Eater, 1960 December 9; 4958 (Box 6)
      - A Fury Slinging Flame, 1960 December; 4956 (Box 7)
      - Sheba, 1961 January 6; 4992 (Box 7)
      - The Quick and The Dead, 1961 January 13; 4961 (Box 7)
      - Play It Glissanco, 1961 January 20; 4012 (Box 7)
      - The Clover Throne, 1961 January 27; 4998 (Box 7)
      - Fly Away Home - Part I, 1961 February 10; 4013 (Box 7)
      - Fly Away Home - Part II, 1961 February 17; 4014 (Box 7)
      - Sleep on Four Pillows, 1961 February 24; 4041 (Box 7)
      - An Absence of Tears, 1961 March 3; 4054 (Box 7)
      - Like A Motherless Child, 1961 March 17; 4044 (Box 7)
      - Effigy in Snow, 1961 March 24; 4042 (Box 7)
      - Eleven, The Hard Way, 1961 April 7; 4052 (Box 7)
      - Most Vanquished, Most Victorious, 1961 April 14; 4064 (Box 8)
      - Don't Count Stars, 1961 April 28; 4060 (Box 8)
      - The Newborn, 1961 May 5; 4039 (Box 8)
      - A Skill for Hunting, 1961 May 12; 4076 (Box 8)
      - Trap at Delgado, 1961 May 26; 4065 (Box 8)
      - The Opponent, 1961 June 2; 4063 (Box 8)
      - Welcome to Amity, 1961 June 9; 4097 (Box 8)
      - Incident on a Bridge, 1961 June 16; 4084 (Box 8)
      - A Month of Sundays, 1961 September 22; 4132 (Box 8)
      - Blue Murder, 1961 September 29; 4133 (Box 8)
      - Good Night, Sweet Blues, 1961 October 6; 4174 (Box 8)
      - Birdcage On My Foot, 1961 October 13; 4181; (2 copies - one containing numerous holograph corrections) (Box 8)
      - First Class Mouliak, 1961 October 20; 4096 (Box 9)
      - Once To Every Man, 1961 October 27; 4173 (Box 9)
      - The Mud Nest, 1961 November 10; 3157 (Box 9)
      - A Bridge Across Five Days, 1961 November 17; 4197 (Box 9)
      - Mom Petit Chou, 1961 November 24; 4171 (Box 9)
      - Some of the People, Some of the Time, 1961 December 1; 4035 (Box 9)
      - The Thin White Line, 1961 December 8; 4205 (Box 9)
      - ...And The Cat Jumped Over The Moon, 1961 December 15; 4198 (Box 9)
      - Burning for Burning, 1961 December 29; 4134 (Box 9)
      - To Walk with the Serpent, 1962 January 5; 4146 (Box 9)
      - A Long Piece of Mischief, 1961 January 19; 4214 (Box 9)
      - 1800 Days To Justice, 1962 January 26; 4213 (Box 9)
      - City of Wheels, 1962 February 2; 4082 (Box 9)
      - How Much A Pound Is Albatross?, 1962 February 9; 4216 (Box 10)
      - Aren't You Surprised To See Me?, 1962 February 16; 4224 (Box 10)
      - You Never Had It So Good, 1962 February 23; 4229 (Box 10)
      - Shoulder The Sky, My Lad, 1962 March 2; 4247 (Box 10)
      - Blues For The Left Foot, 1962 March 9; 4230 (Box 10)
      - Go Read The River, 1962 March 16; 4243 (Box 10)
      - Even Stones Have Eyes, 1962 March 30; 4222 (Box 10)
      - Love Is A Skinny Kid, 1962 April 6; 4255 (Box 10)
      - Kiss The Maiden, All Forlorn, 1962 April 13; 4256 (Box 10)
      - Two On The House, 1962 April 20; 4088 (Box 10)
      - There I Am, There I Always Am..., 1962 May 4; 4504 (Box 10)
      - Between Hello and Goodbye, 1962 May 11; 4502 (Box 10)
      - A Feat of Strength, 1962 May 18; 4215 (Box 11)
      - Hell Is Empty, All The Devils Are Here, 1962 May 25; 4508 (Box 11)
      - From An Enchantress Fleeing, 1962 June 1; 4504 (Box 11)
      - One Tiger To A Hill, 1962 September 21; 4516 (Box 11)
      - Journey To Ninevah, 1962 September 28; 4514 (Box 11)
      - Man Out of Time, 1962 October 5; 4521 (Box 11)
      - Ever Ride The Waves In Oklahoma?, 1962 October 12; 4515 (Box 11)
      - Voice At The End Of The Line, 1962 October 19; 4510 (Box 11)
      - Lizard's Leg and Owlet's Wing, 1962 October 26; 4513; (2 copies) (Box 11)
      - Across Walnuts And Wine, 1962 November 2; 4517 (Box 11)
      - Welcome To The Wedding, 1962 November 9; 4520 (Box 11)
      - Every Father's Daughter, 1962 November 16; 4512 (Box 11)
      - Poor Little Kangaroo Rat, 1962 November 23; 4507 (Box 12)
      - Hey Moth, Come Eat The Flame, 1962 November 30; 4524 (Box 12)
      - Only By Cunning Glimpses, 1962 December 7; 4523 (Box 12)
      - Where Is Chick Lorimer, Where Has She Gone?, 1962 December 14; 4522 (Box 12)
      - Give The Old Cat A Tender Mouse, 1962 December 21; 4525 (Box 12)
      - A Bunch Of Lonely Pagliaccis, 1963 January 4; 4526 (Box 12)
      - You Can't Pick Cotton In Tahiti, 1963 January 11; 4531 (Box 12)
      - A Gift For A Warrior, 1963 January 18; 4500 (Box 12)
      - Suppose I Said I Was The Queen of Spain, 1963 February 8; 4534 (Box 12)
      - Somehow It Gets To Be Tomorrow, 1963 February 15; 4533 (Box 12)
      - ...Shall Forfeit His Dog And Ten Shillings To The King, 1963 February 22; 4527 (Box 12)
      - In The Closing of a Trunk, 1963 March 8; 4538 (Box 12)
      - The Cage Around Maria, 1963 March 15; 4536 (Box 12)
      - Fifty Miles From Home, 1963 March 22; 4540 (Box 13)
      - Narcissus on An Old Red Fire Engine, 1963 March 29; 4539 (Box 13)
      - The Cruelest Sea Of All, 1963 April 5; 4541 (Box 13)
      - Peace, Pity, Pardon, 1963 April 12; 4542 (Box 13)
      - What A Shining Young Was Our Gallant Lieutenant, 1963 April 26; 4544 (Box 13)
      - But What Do You Do In March?, 1963 May 3; 4545 (Box 13)
      - Who Will Cheer My Bonnie Bride?, 1963 May 10; 4547 (Box 13)
      - Shadows Of An Afternoon, 1963 May 17; 4548 (Box 13)
      - Soda Pop and Paper Flags, 1963 May 31 (Box 13)
      - Two Strangers and an Old Enemy, 1963 September 27; 4546 (Box 13)
      - Same Picture, Different Frame, 1963 October 4; 4556 (Box 13)
      - Come Out, Come Out, Wherever You Are, 1963 October 11; 4560 (Box 13)
      - Where Are The Sounds of Celli Brahms?, 1963 October 18; 4555 (Box 14)
      - Build Your Houses With Their Backs To The Sea, 1963 October 25; 4561 (Box 14)
      - And Make Thunder His Tribute, 1963 November 1; 4554 (Box 14)
      - The Stone Guest, 1963 November 8; 4550 (Box 14)
      - I Wouldn't Start From Here, 1963 November 15; 4562 (Box 14)
      - A Cage In Search Of A Bird, 1963 November 29; 4549 (Box 14)
      - A Long Way From St. Louie, 1963 December 6; 4563 (Box 14)
      - Come Home, Grete Inger Gruenschaffen, 1963 December 13; 4552 (Box 14)
      - 93 Per Cent In Smiling, 1963 December 20; 4566 (Box 14)
      - Child Of A Night, 1964 January 3; 4564 (Box 14)
      - Is It True There Are Poxies At The Bottom Of Landfair Lake?, 1964 January 10; 4572 (Box 14)
      - Like This It Means Father.. Like This --Bitter... Like This --Tiger.., 1964 January 17; 4567 (Box 14)
      - Kiss The Monster -- Make Him Sleep, 1964 January 24; 4558 (Box 15)
      - Cries Of Persons Close To One, 1964 January 3; 4565 (Box 15)
      - Who In His Right Mind Needs A Nice Girl, 1964 February 7; 4573 (Box 15)
      - This Is Going To Hurt Me More Than It Hurts You, 1964 February 14; 4568 (Box 15)
      - Follow The White Dove With The Broken Wing, 1964 February 21; 4574 (Box 15)
      - Where There's A Will, There's A Way - Part I, 1964 March 6; 4569 (Box 15)
      - Where There's A Will, There's A Way - Part II, 1964; 4575 (Box 15)
      - I'm Here To Kill A King, 1963 September 9; 2 copies. (Box 15)
  - Salem's Lot, Addition, 11/82.
    - Outline for the screenplay. n.p., 1976 February 2; by Stirling Silliphant; 49 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy), with holograph corrections. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Outline for the screenplay. n.p., 1976 February 2; by Stirling Silliphant; 52 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Outline for the screenplay. n.p., 1976 February 2; by Stirling Silliphant; 52 pages. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 12; by Stirling Silliphant; 240 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 12; by Stirling Silliphant; 243 pages. Typescript. First draft. (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 12; by Stirling Silliphant; 243 pages. Typescript (carbon). First draft. (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Another copy., Typescript (photocopy) (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 243 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript, with holograph corrections. First draft. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 243 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 157 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy). First draft. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 July 16; by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 157 pages. Typescript (carbon). First draft. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 157 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy). First draft. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 158 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy), with holograph corrections. First revised draft. (Box 90, Folder 4-5)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 March 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 157 pages. Typescript (photocopy). First draft. (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Another copy. (Box 90, Folder 5)
        Marked #1 on front cover and stamped Warner Bros. Inc./Burbank, California/Story Library.
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 162 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy). First revised draft. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 162 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. First draft. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 132 pages. Typescript. First draft. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 July 12; by Stirling Silliphant; 143 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 132 pages. Typescript (carbon). First draft. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 132 pages. Typescript (photocopy). First draft. (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Another copy. (Box 91, Folder 3)
        Marked #2 on front cover and stamped Warner Bros. Inc./Burbank, California/Story Library.
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 162 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript with holograph corrections. First revised draft. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 162 pages. Typescript (carbon). First revised draft. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 April 26; by Stirling Silliphant; 162 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy). First revised draft. (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 July 12; by Stirling Silliphant; 143 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 July 16; by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript. (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 July 16; by Stirling Silliphant; 135 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay from the novel by Stephen King. n.p., 1976 July 16; by Stirling Silliphant; 135 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Revised pages., ca. 1976-1977; ca. 50 pages. Typescript, typescipt (carbon), typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay., ca. 1976-1977; pages 26-162. Typescript. Incomplete. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Characters---In order of their appearance in the novel/Sequences of Salem's Lot. n.p., undated.; [i-ii], [1]-47. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Another copy., Typescript (carbon). (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Another copy., Typescript (photocopy). (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Shadow and Substance
    - (TV series), 13 leaves. (Box 34)
      Production notes.
  - So Many Miles of Grey Elephants
    - 1971 February 19, Revised typescript [teleplay]. (Box 43)
    - 1971 February 19, Revised typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 43)
    - 1971 February 19, Typescript carbon, revised [teleplay] (Box 43)
    - 1971 January 19, First draft typescript [teleplay] (Box 43)
    - 1971 January 18, Revised typescript with holograph corrections, section [teleplay] (Box 43)
    - 1971 February 11, First draft typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 43)
    - 1971 February 19, Revised typescript [teleplay]. (Box 43)
    - 1971 January 19, First draft carbon [teleplay] (Box 43)
  - Suspicion, Revue Productions, Inc.
    - 1957 October 17, 1 teleplay. (Box 1)
  - The Brothers Brannagen, Brad-Jacey Production, Inc.
    - 1960 June 21, Revised copy. (Box 1)
    - 1960 March 15, 1 teleplay. (Box 1)
  - The Chrysler Theater
    - (Box 16)
      (Each folder also contains correspondence, contracts and agreements, between the author and the producer.)
      - "The Sojourner", 1 synopsis (?) of the story. (Box 16)
        (based on a story by Carson McCullers)
      - "The Sojourner", 1964 March 27; 1 revised teleplay with holograph corrections. (Box 16)
      - "The Sojourner", 1964 March 27; 1 teleplay (carbon). (Box 16)
      - "The Sojourner", 1964 April 8; 1 teleplay. (Box 16)
      - "Murder In the First", 1964 June 22; 1 story outline. (Box 16)
        (based on book, Death and the Supreme Court, by Barrett Prettyman Jr.).
      - "Murder In the First", 1964 June 16; 1 story outline. (Box 16)
      - "Murder In the First", 1964 July 17; 1 teleplay. (Box 16)